



## **Professional Summary**

Recent graduate of University College Cork, having studied a four year BA International degree with Spanish and History. As part of my degree I studied in Santiago de Compostela, Spain, where I participated in the Erasmus programme, from September 2021 to June 2022. Winner of the John A. Murphy Prize in University College Cork for academic writing of an Irish History dissertation.

After working as a sixteen year old doing some warehouse and delivery work, I transitioned to bar work when I was eighteen as I wanted to work more in a customer facing role. I worked in Cork's largest hotel & conference venue (Rochestown Park Hotel & Conference Centre – 4 star hotel), across various departments, primarily the bar and restaurant. I am currently working part time in Thompson's Bar and Restaurant in Cork City.

Other skills and achievements include achieving a B2 level in written and spoken Spanish; basic knowledge of Italian and German; a published article in my university magazine; running an efficient blog on WordPress for a number of years dealing with travel, history, and music; having travelled for a sufficient amount of time all over Europe, as well as in Central and Latin America.

# Skills and Qualities

- Customer service
- Self-motivated
- High-volume dining
- Heavy manual lifting
- Food safety understanding
- Warehouse operations
- Problem solving
- Brand marketing

- Upbeat, outgoing and positive
- Expert multitasker
- Efficient under pressure
- Spirits, wine and food service
- Social media proficiency
- Creative writing
- WordPress knowledge
- Travel-orientated writing

#### Attributes as a worker

- Knowledge of WordPress and social media platforms, which I have used to my advantage in writing my own blog for several years.
- Capable of working long hours including the possible late nights, as well as extra hours.
- Competent, driven, and willing to do whatever necessary to ensure the task at hand will be done properly, with efficiency and professionalism.
- Not afraid to try new things, proven so with numerous different jobs and experiences.

### Work Experience

Bartender, Cashier, Waiter: Rochestown Park Hotel, Rochestown, Co. Cork. July 2018 – August 2021.

Bartender, Waiter: Thompsons Bar and Restaurant, McCurtain Street, Cork City. July 2022 – Present.

- Improving stock management efficiency, accurately forecasting demand to meet supply levels.
- Managed restaurant closing duties, from cleaning dining areas to cashing up tills.

Student Brand Marketeer: Seed Marketing for Amazon Prime Student. September 2020 - March 2021.

- Ensured business continuity by acquiring insight into social marketing trends and effectively adjusting strategies.
- Maintained brand consistency by writing content in line with brand guidelines.
- Helped in the growth of the brand across Ireland, especially in the universities of Cork.

#### Education

Gaelscoil Carraig Uí Leighin, Co. Cork. 2005 - 2013

Carrigaline Community School. 2013 – 2019.

University College Cork. 2019 – 2023.

- Completed a BA International degree with a grade of 1:1 honours.
- Won the John A. Murphy Prize for achieving the highest marked Irish History dissertation in my university year.
- Member of UCC Futsal Sports Team.